https://ez-tree.com/ez-tree-privacy/

HomePrivacy ez tree Commitment To PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.The Information We Collect:This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the ez tree website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Credit/Debit Card Information
(etc.)The Way We Use Information:We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.You can register with our website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.Our Commitment To Data SecurityTo prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.How You Can Access Or Correct Your InformationYou can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by the provided online tools to do so. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.How To Contact UsShould you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at service @ privacy.ez-tree.com
Christmas TreesArtificial Christmas TreesChristmas Tree ColorsBlack Christmas TreeChampagne Christmas TreeCopper Christmas TreeHot Pink Christmas TreeLime Green Christmas TreePink Christmas TreePurple Christmas TreeFlocked Christmas TreeInstant Shape Christmas TreeLED Prelit Christmas TreePencil Christmas TreeTree Size10 ft Artificial Christmas Trees12 ft Artificial Christmas Trees14 ft Artificial Christmas Trees15 ft Artificial Christmas Trees20 ft Artificial Christmas Tree3 ft Artificial Christmas Trees3.5 ft Artificial Christmas Trees4 ft Artificial Christmas Tree4.5 ft Artificial Christmas Tree5 ft Artificial Christmas Trees5.5 ft Artificial Christmas Trees6 ft Artificial Christmas Trees6.5 ft Artificial Christmas Trees7 ft Artificial Christmas Tree7.5 ft Artificial Christmas Tree8 ft Artificial Christmas Trees8.5 ft Artificial Christmas Trees9 ft Artificial Christmas Trees 9 ft9.5 ft Artificial Christmas TreesUpside Down TreeChristmas Tree SaleFiber Optic Christmas TreesHalloween Tree
Search
